[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many arms do octopuses have?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "0", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these people was a dentist?", "correct_answer": "Paul Revere", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Alva Edison", "Samuel F.B. Morse", "DeWit Clinton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Cat Woman?", "correct_answer": "Selina Kyle", "incorrect_answers": ["Samantha Wayne", "Pam Isley", "Sarah Connor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is no generally accepted cure for fybromyalgia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Luke Skywalkers friend from Tattoine in Star Wars episode four, A New Hope?", "correct_answer": "Biggs Darklight", "incorrect_answers": ["Bail Organa", "Wedge Antilles", "Wes Janson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The four main characters in the movie American Pie vowed to lose their virginity before what major event in their lives?", "correct_answer": "Senior Prom", "incorrect_answers": ["High School Graduation", "Start of College", "Getting Married"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the femoral artery located?", "correct_answer": "Thigh", "incorrect_answers": ["Uterus", "Calf", "Along the spinal column"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Star Wars saga, there is a Tusken Raider who is a Jedi master.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the capital city of India?", "correct_answer": "New Delhi", "incorrect_answers": ["Jaipur", "Mumbai", "Calcutta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Chronicles of Narnia: The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe the four main characters are Peter, Edmund, Lucy and who else?", "correct_answer": "Susan", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary", "Liza", "Elizabeth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to the Little Mermaid at the end of Hans Christian Andersens fairy tale The Little Mermaid?", "correct_answer": "Her body turns into foam.", "incorrect_answers": ["She returns to the underwater world and marries a merman.", "She dies and is damned for eternity.", "She marries the prince and they live happily ever after."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these wild roses is native to China?", "correct_answer": "Rosa laevigata", "incorrect_answers": ["Rosa eglanteria", "Rosa canina", "Rosa gigantea"]}]